lifeisgood.com 2017-10-10

# Life is good Privacy Policy

At Life is good, we are committed to protecting your privacy. We use the information we collect about you to process orders and to provide a more personalized shopping experience. Please read on for more details about our privacy policy.

**What Information Do We Collect? How Do We Use It?**  
When you order, we need to know your name, e-mail address, mailing address, phone number, credit-card number and expiration date. This allows us to process and fulfill your orders and to notify you of your order status.

You may also voluntarily sign up to be informed about certain offers, which we use to send the information you requested.

When you enter a contest or other promotional feature, we may ask for your name, address and e-mail address, and personal preferences, so we can administer the contest and notify winners. We personalize your shopping experience by using your purchases to shape our recommendations about other merchandise that might be of interest to you. We also monitor customer traffic patterns and site usage to help us develop the design and layout of the site.

We may also use the information we collect to occasionally notify you about important changes to the Website, new Life is good services, and special offers we think you'll find valuable. If you would like to opt-out from receiving Life is good emails, please contact Customer Service by emailing customer_service@lifeisgood.com, by managing your email preferences within the "My Account" section of our Website, or by following the unsubscribe instructions in each email.

**Your Consent**  
By using our Website, you consent to the collection and use of this information by Life is good. If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page, so you are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it and under what circumstances we disclose it.

**How Does Life is good Protect Customer Information?**  
We have physical, electronic and procedural security safeguards to protect and secure the information we collect.  
Our Website uses Secure Sockets Layering (SSL) to encrypt your personal credit information, including your credit card number, before it travels over the Internet. SSL technology is the industry standard for secure online transactions. Because we use SSL, placing an order online at our Website is just as safe as giving your credit card number over the phone.

**Will Life is good Disclose the Information it Collects to Outside Parties?**  
We are committed to protecting your privacy. We use the information we collect on the site to make shopping at Life is good possible and to enhance your overall shopping experience. We do not sell, trade or rent your personal information to others. The Website depends, in part, on functionality provided by third party vendors.  Some of your information may pass through the systems of these vendors in order to deliver a quality shopping experience to you.

Life is Good has partnered with UPS and i-parcel for orders shipping outside the United States. International shoppers now get the benefit of seeing product prices in their local currency, guaranteed order totals and cost effective international shipping. To see the i-parcel privacy policy, please go here:[ https://www.i-parcel.com/en/i-parcel-online-privacy-notice/](https://www.i-parcel.com/en/i-parcel-online-privacy-notice/)

**Tell Us What You Think**  
We welcome your comments regarding this Website. However, any comments, feedback, notes, messages, ideas, suggestions or other communications (collectively, "Comments") sent to Lifeisgood.com shall be and remain the exclusive property of Lifeisgood.com. Your submission of any such Comments shall constitute an assignment to Lifeisgood.com of all worldwide rights, titles and interests in all copyrights and other intellectual property rights in the Comments. Lifeisgood.com will be entitled to use, reproduce, disclose, publish and distribute any material you submit for any purpose whatsoever, without restriction and without compensating you in any way. For this reason, we ask that you not send us any comments that you do not wish to assign to us, including any confidential information or any original creative materials such as stories, product ideas, computer code or original artwork.

**Inaccuracy Disclaimer**  
From time to time there may be information on our Website or in our catalog that contains typographical errors, inaccuracies, or omissions that may relate to product descriptions, pricing, and availability. Life is good reserves the right to correct any errors, inaccuracies or omissions and to change or update information at any time without prior notice (including after you have submitted your order).

**Are Children Allowed to Use Lifeisgood.com?**  
Life is good does not sell products for purchase by children. We sell children's products for purchase by adults. If you are under 18, you may use Lifeisgood.com only with the involvement of a parent or guardian.  
In cases where you have authorized a minor to use the Website, you recognize that you are fully responsible for: (i) the online conduct of such minor; (ii) controlling the minor's access to and use of the Website; and (iii) the consequences of any misuse by the minor. You acknowledge that Life is good has no obligation to monitor the content accessible on or through the Website.

**Copyright Notice**  
All of the Content you see and hear on the Lifeisgood.com website, including, for example, all of the page headers, images, illustrations, graphics, audio clips, video clips and text, are subject to trademark, service mark, trade dress, copyright and/or other intellectual property rights or licenses held by Life is good. The entire Content of this Website is copyrighted as a collective work under U.S. copyright laws, and Life is good owns a copyright in the selection, coordination, arrangement and enhancement of the Content.  
The Content of this Website, and the site as a whole, is intended solely for personal, noncommercial use by the users of our site. You may download, print and store selected portions of the Content, provided you (1) only use these copies of the Content for your own personal, non—commercial use, (2) do not copy or post the Content on any network computer or broadcast the Content in any media, and (3) do not modify or alter the Content in any way, or delete or change any copyright or trademark notice.

No right, title or interest in any downloaded materials is transferred to you as a result of any such downloading. Lifeisgood.com reserves complete title and full intellectual property rights in any Content you download from this Website.

Except as noted above, you may not copy, download, reproduce, modify, publish, distribute, transmit, transfer or create derivative works from the Content without first obtaining written permission from Life is good.
